nelly.com 2004-06-06

# Fo Sheedo.com

#### FOSHEEDO, LLC PRIVACY STATEMENT

This privacy statement is applicable to Fosheedo.com and any other site that Fosheedo owns and operates. 

Children Under 13

Fosheedo does not intend to collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. If you are under 13, you should not enter any personally identifiable information about yourself on any Fosheedo web site or in any Fosheedo product, and should ask a parent to do so for you. If you are under 13, Fosheedo must have express written permission from a parent before you may provide us with any information about yourself. The authorizing parent must email us at customerservice@fosheedo.com certifying the parent's age and authority, and giving us express permission to acquire and retain any such personal information from you as we may normally obtain from users of any of our sites. 

Information Collection 

Fosheedo does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide this information on a voluntary basis. For example, we might ask for such information when we run a contest, when you register for subscription services, during product registration, in our online stores, and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), surveys, and voting and polling activities. Fosheedo will make every effort to ensure that whatever information you provide will be maintained in a secure environment. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Fosheedo cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you provide such information at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. 

Information Sharing 

Fosheedo may from time to time share or provide your personally identifiable contact information to unaffiliated third parties, including successors in interest, who may offer you related goods and services. 

Fosheedo may also retain an outside company to manage a database containing certain customer information to create and distribute mailings or e-mail offerings by Fosheedo or third parties. In those situations, the outside party is performing work for Fosheedo. 

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status, technical support, product information, changes to the subscriber agreement, and any other matter that might affect our service to you and/or our records on you and/or any products you purchased from us. 

Fosheedo may also disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Fosheedo’s rights or property, other Fosheedo users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Fosheedo may also disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Information Use 

Fosheedo may use your identifiable contact information to send you promotional and/or marketing information about products, services and offerings from Fosheedo. Fosheedo reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics, either internally or by sending this data to a third party for further analysis. We do this in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of our Web sites and to create tailored marketing offerings. We may share this information with advertisers. We may also use this information to let advertisers know how many visitors have seen their banners and how many have clicked on them. Fosheedo will generally provide only aggregated data from these analyses to advertisers; advertisers will not normally be able to identify any individual from these analyses. 

Also, you should be aware that Fosheedo may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through a Fosheedo site. Fosheedo is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of any third party when providing personally identifiable information. 

Fosheedo collects IP addresses for system administration, record keeping, and advertising reporting. Your IP address is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the World Wide Web. Fosheedo's servers record incoming IP addresses. The IP addresses are analyzed only in aggregate; no connection is made between you and your computer's IP address. By tracking IP addresses, we can determine which sites refer the most people to Fosheedo. (Think of an IP address like your zip code; it tells us in general terms where you're from.) 

You should be very cautious when you voluntarily disclose personal information (for example, name or e-mail address) on bulletin boards, in chat areas, or the upload areas of any Fosheedo site. That information, along with any other information you may disclose in your posting, can be collected, correlated, and used by third parties, and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Fosheedo. 

Cookies 

You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Fosheedo's Internet servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a Web site can use to recognize repeat users. Fosheedo uses cookies to recognize visitors and more quickly provide personalized content or grant you unimpeded access to registered areas of our Web sites. With cookies enabled, you will not need to fill in password or contact information, should areas of our sites ask for this information. Information gathered through cookies also helps us measure use of our sites. Cookie data allow us to track usage behavior and compile data that we can use to improve the site and target advertising. 

Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside of the Web site that he or she is visiting. Sometimes, advertisers or third parties hosting data for Fosheedo will issue cookies. Fosheedo cannot control the use of these cookies or the information that they gather. 

You can easily turn off cookies. Most browsers have a feature that allows the user to refuse cookies or issues a warning when cookies are being sent. Remember, though, cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features available on Fosheedo's sites. Some areas of our site may not function properly without cookies. Enabling cookies ensures a smooth, efficient visit to our site. 

Opting Out 

Upon request, Fosheedo will allow any user to opt out of further promotional contacts at any time. Additionally upon request, Fosheedo will use reasonable efforts to allow you to update or correct personal information to the extent that changing the data will not compromise privacy or security interests. Also, upon your request, Fosheedo will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete you and your personal information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete all of your information without some residual data because of backups and records of deletions. Furthermore, your e-mail address will be added to a suppression list that stops any message directed to you before it leaves Fosheedo. It is your responsibility, however, to make certain that we have your most current e-mail address. 

Should you wish to opt out of any mailing from Fosheedo or a mailing you received through information provided to a third party affiliate, please contact Fosheedo list maintenance. 

Links to Other Sites 

Fosheedo may from time to time offer links to other sites from sites within the Fosheedo domain. Fosheedo has no control over these external sites or their content, and cannot be held responsible for any actions they may take or any information they might collect. You may arrive at one of these sites through clicking on a banner advertisement, as part of a co-branding arrangement, or simply by selecting a link on a Fosheedo web page. These sites might issue their own cookies or collect data or personal information. Use caution when visiting an external site. 

Fosheedo Security Policy 

Fosheedo is aware of your privacy concerns and strives to collect only as much data as is required to make your Internet and/or product use experience as efficient and satisfying as possible, in the most unobtrusive manner as possible. 

Consent to Processing in the United States 

By providing any personal information to Fosheedo pursuant to this Privacy Policy, all users, including, without limitation, users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection and processing of such information in the United States of America. 

The foregoing policies are effective as of July 11, 2003. Fosheedo reserves the right to change this policy at any time. By using our site, you signify your assent to the Fosheedo Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Fosheedo sites and products following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
